Guide to the National Education Association-Committees records, 1857-1996 NEA1003.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Committee on Planning and Organizational Development, 1887-1985; 1968-1978; Series 5; 17 Linear Feet
  - Annual Meeting-President's Transcript, 1975; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting-Slideshow/Dues Increase, July 1975; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 3)
  - As a Planning Arm of the NEA, circa 1970; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 4)
  - Association of Classroom Teachers, 1970-1973; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 5)
  - Association of Classroom Teachers-A Proposal for Restructure of the NEA, circa 1971; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 6)
  - Background and Resource Papers [file 1/2], 1967-1972; Series 5 (Box 1586, Folder 2)
  - Background and Resource Papers [file 2/2], 1967-1972; Series 5 (Box 1586, Folder 3)
  - Background and Resource Papers [file 1/2], 1969-1971; Series 5 (Box 1586, Folder 4)
  - Background and Resource Papers [file 2/2], 1969-1971; Series 5 (Box 1586, Folder 5)
  - Beebe, William B., March 1970; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 7)
    Beebe, William B.
  - Bi-Monthly Reports, 1975-1976; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 8)
  - Bi-Weekly Payroll Reports (Janice Mintz), 1973; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 9)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    This file contains Social Security numbers and sensitve personal data. Use will be limited by staff.
    Mintz, Janice
  - Bicentennial Committee, 1976; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 10)
  - Bill of Student Teacher Rights, 1977; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 11)
  - Board of Directors-Methods for Reaching Consensus at Meetings, 1970; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 12)
  - Boardroom Reports, 1977-1978; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 13)
  - Budget Committee, January 1969-September 1969; Series 5 (Box 1167, Folder 14)
  - Budget Committee Meeting, January 1970; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 1)
  - Budget Committee Meeting, February 1970; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 2)
  - Budget, Credentials, 1976; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 3)
  - Budget, Evaluation, 1974; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 4)
  - Budget, NEA, 1971-1972; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 5)
  - Budget, NEA, 1973-1974; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 6)
  - Budget, NEA, 1977-1978; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 7)
  - Budget, Planning Office, 1976-1977; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 8)
  - Budget Priorities, January 1969; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 9)
  - Budget-Transaction Registers, 1974-1975; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 10)
  - Bureau of Indian Affairs, April 1976; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 11)
  - Bylaws Committee, August 1969-April 1970; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 12)
  - Cabinet-NEA, September 1970; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 13)
  - Census (Materials), 1971; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 14)
  - Center for Human Relations, 1969-1971; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 15)
  - Center for the Study of Instruction (CSI), 1969-1970; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 16)
  - Chart of Accounts, 1976-1977; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 17)
  - Chart of Accounts, 1977-1978; Series 5 (Box 1168, Folder 18)
  - Chicago, January 1974; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 1)
  - Chief Executive, 1970; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 2)
  - Christian Remarks and Final Committee on Planning and Organizational Development, May 1975; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 3)
    Christian, Mary
  - Chronological, 1969-1971; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 4)
  - Citizenship Committee, 1969; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 5)
  - Coalition of American Public Employees (CAPE), 1972-1974; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 6)
  - Coalition of American Public Employees (CAPE), 1977; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 7)
  - Coalition of American Public Employees (CAPE), February 1977-May 1977; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 8)
  - Committee Assignments (Memos to Executive Staff), 1975; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Director-Staff Relations, November 1971; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Dual Representation and Size of Assembly, July 1968-July 1969; Series 5 (Box 1169, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Educational Finance, January 1969-February 1969; Series 5 (Box 1170, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Financial Needs and Resources [file 1/2], January 1967-December 1968; Series 5 (Box 1170, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Financial Needs and Resources [file 2/2], January 1967-December 1968; Series 5 (Box 1170, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Formal Relationships with Outside Groups, February 1969-June 1970; Series 5 (Box 1170, Folder 4)
  - Committee on International Relations, August 1970; Series 5 (Box 1170, Folder 5)
  - Committee on NEA Economic Controls (Wage-Price Controls), August 1971-March 1972; Series 5 (Box 1170, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Planning and Organizational Development, July 1973-March 1974; Series 5 (Box 1170, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Planning and Organizational Development-General, November 1968-July 1974; Series 5 (Box 1170, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Short and Long Range Space Needs of the NEA and Departments, April 1969-April 1970; Series 5 (Box 1170, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Spelling Reform, 1897-1905; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Teacher Oversupply and Underemployment, November 1971-February 1972; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Terms and Funding of the Representative Assembly, 1975; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 3)
  - Committee Papers-General, 1950-1982; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 4)
  - Committee Recommendations, September 1976; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 5)
  - Committee to Study NEA Dues Increase, 1974-1975; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 6)
  - Committees, 1975; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 7)
  - Committees and Commissions-General, 1968-1971; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 8)
  - Conflict of Interest Policy, March 1974; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 9)
  - Congressional Roster, January 1970; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 10)
  - Constitution-Excerpts from State Association Constitutions, 1967-1969; Series 5 (Box 1171, Folder 11)
  - Constitution and Bylaws, August 1973; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 1)
  - Constitutional Convention-Double Slide Presentation, May 1972; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 2)
  - Constitutional Convention-Draft Resolutions about Ratification of Constitution and Bylaws, 1972-1973; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 3)
  - Constitutional Convention-General, 1971-1972; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 4)
  - Constitutional Convention-Problems and Issues Raised by Document, February 1971-June 1972; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 5)
  - Constitutional Convention-Proposed Constitution, circa 1972; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 6)
  - Consultant-Lieberman, 1971-1972; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 7)
  - Consultant-Zand, Dale, 1973; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 8)
  - Consultants, October 1969-September 1970; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1972; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1973; Series 5 (Box 1172, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence [file 1/2], 1974; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence [file 2/2], 1974; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence-Miscellaneous, August 1968-July 1972; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence-Miscellaneous, May 1974-November 1974; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence-Planning, January 1975-December 1976; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 5)
  - Council for Analysis of Organizational Structure, September 1965-December 1969; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 6)
  - Credentials Committee, June 1976-July 1976; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 7)
  - Credit Union Committee, 1955-1965; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 8)
  - Critical Issues-Miami Beach, FL, January 1976-June 1976; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 9)
  - Critical Issues-Minneapolis, December 1976-March 1977; Series 5 (Box 1173, Folder 10)
  - Critical Issues Conference, January 1969; Series 5 (Box 1174, Folder 1)
  - Critical Issues Conference-Chicago, IL, June 1974; Series 5 (Box 1174, Folder 2)
  - Critical Issues Conference-Los Angeles, CA, May 1975-July 1975; Series 5 (Box 1174, Folder 3)
  - Critical Issues Conference-Materials [file 1/2], January 1969; Series 5 (Box 1174, Folder 4)
  - Critical Issues Conference-Materials [file 2/2], January 1969; Series 5 (Box 1174, Folder 5)
  - Critical Issues Conference-Planning, January 1969; Series 5 (Box 1174, Folder 6)
  - Critical Issues Conference-Recommendations and Staff Reactions [file 1/2], January 1969-November 1969; Series 5 (Box 1174, Folder 7)
  - Critical Issues Conference-Recommendations and Staff Reactions [file 2/2], January 1969-November 1969; Series 5 (Box 1174, Folder 8)
  - CSI, Decision Points, LL misc. [sic], 1996; Series 5 (Box 4033, Floppy disk 1)
  - Critical Issues Conference-Unit Follow-Up, May 1969-February 1970; Series 5 (Box 1174, Folder 9)
  - Digest-Excellence in Local-State-National Relationship, June 1973; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 1)
  - Dues Analysis Study, 1969-1975; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 2)
  - Dues Committee Report to Board, May 1965-December 1974; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 3)
  - Dues Increase, Committee on, 1974; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 4)
  - Dues Increase Packets, 1975; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 5)
  - Dues Increase-Presentation, 1973-1975; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 6)
  - Dues Increase-Program, 1975-1976; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 7)
  - Dues Increase-Slide-Tape Presentation, January 1975-August 1975; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 8)
  - Dues, Membership, December 1973-December 1975; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 9)
  - Dues/Membership Report to the Board, November 1974; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 10)
  - Dushane Advisory Fund Committee, 1969; Series 5 (Box 1175, Folder 11)
  - Dushane Defense Fund Committee, October 1968-January 1969; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 1)
  - Educational Finance, 1973; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 2)
  - Energy Crisis, February 1974; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 3)
  - Erhard Seminars Training, June 1975; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation, 1974; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 5)
  - Evaluation-Correspondence, January 1975; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation-First Quarter-Formative Evaluation, November 1973; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 7)
  - Evaluation Information, January 1975-July 1976; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 8)
  - Evaluation-Local Association, circa 1974; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 9)
  - Evaluation-School Instrument for School/District Evaluation, 1975-1976; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 10)
  - "Excellence in Local-State-National Relationships", February 1974; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 11)
  - Excellence in Local-State-National Relationships-State Information, July 1973-April 1974; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 12)
  - Excellence Memoranda, May 1973-December 1974; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 13)
  - "Future Association Development", April 1972; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 14)
  - The Future of Learning and Teaching, 1968; series 5 (Box 4351, Folder 1)
  - Future Teachers of America, 1970; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 15)
  - General, May 1974-September 1975; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 16)
  - Governance Structures, circa 1973; Series 5 (Box 1176, Folder 17)
  - Guide to Teaching about the United Nations and World Affairs, 1953; series 4 (Box 4203, Folder 5)
  - Guidelines for Closer Relationships between State Directors and State Associations, January 1969-May 1970; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 1)
  - Harris, James, February 1976; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 2)
    Harris, James A.
  - Harris Surveys, 1977-1978; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 3)
  - Health Education and Welfare, 1977; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 4)
  - Higher Education-Draft Organization Manual for Local Faculty Leaders, February 1974-May 1975; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 5)
  - Higher Education-"Election and Delegate Support Procedures", March 1976; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 6)
  - Higher Education-Iowa, 1976; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 7)
  - Higher Education-Study, June 1973-October 1973; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 8)
  - Inflation, 1974; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 9)
  - Insurance (Handbooks, memoranda, etc), 1975; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 10)
  - IBM-Word Processing System Study, December 1975; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 11)
  - Joint Chartering of Locals, 1968-1969; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 12)
  - Joint Committee on Educational Television, 1950-1952; Series 5 (Box 1177, Folder 13)
  - Kansas-NEA, 1974-1975; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 1)
  - Legislation-"Federal Bargaining Bill", 1976; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 2)
  - Letters by Chairman, March 1971; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 3)
  - Liaison with Major Committees, July 1970; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 4)
  - Life Insurance Policy, 1977; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 5)
  - Local-State-National-Report-Feedback from Regional Managers, November 1973; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 11)
  - Local-State-National-Supplemental Materials, circa 1973; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 6)
  - Local-State-National-Supplemental Relationships, circa 1973; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 7)
  - Local-State-National-Supplemental Relationship-Mary Christian Remarks, February 1975; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 8)
  - Local-State-National-Supplemental Relationship-Performance of Roles by Three Levels, circa 1973; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 9)
  - Local-State-National-Supplemental Relationship-Process Papers, March 1973; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 10)
  - Long-Range Educational Policy Function at NEA, October 1970-November 1970; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 12)
  - Long-Range Planning Committee, 1974-1977; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 13)
  - Louisiana, 1977; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 14)
  - Materials for Long-Range Planning Committee Meeting, 1975-1977; Series 5 (Box 1178, Folder 15)
  - McGarigal Presentation to NEA/NCSEA About Financial Situation, August 1977; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 1)
  - Meeting, January 1969; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 2)
  - Meeting, November 1969; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 3)
  - Meeting, February 1971; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 4)
  - Meeting-Executive Staff, September 1971-February 1976; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 5)
  - Meeting-Hawaii, September 1975-October 1977; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 6)
  - Meeting-NEA Convention, 1973; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 7)
  - Meeting-New Business Item #11 (Migrant Workers), 1974; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 8)
  - Meeting-Pennsylvania State Education Association (Harrisburg, PA), November 1973-April 1975; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 9)
  - Meeting-Western States Advisory Council (Austin, TX), April 1973; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 10)
  - Meeting-Wyoming Education Association, July 1975-April 1976; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 11)
  - Membership and Dues Processing Standards [file 1/2], November 1973-March 1975; Series 5 (Box 1179, Folder 12)
  - Membership and Dues Processing Standards [file 2/2], November 1973-March 1975; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 1)
  - Minutes of Meeting, April 1967-October 1970; Series 5 (Box 1586, Folder 6)
  - Morale, September 1977; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 2)
  - NCSEA, October 1976-January 1978; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 3)
  - NCSEA-Crowley Papers, circa 1975; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 4)
  - NCSEA-General, 1976; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 5)
  - NCSEA-Information Service Report State Staff Salaries, April 1975; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 6)
  - NCSEA-Questionnaire, May 1974-October 1974; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 7)
  - NCATE, 1974-1975; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 8)
  - NEA-Board Committee System, September 1974; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 9)
  - NEA-Building Services (Building Rules and Regulations), August 1974; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 10)
  - NEA-Committees, Commissions Task Force, June 1973-June 1975; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 11)
  - NEA-Constitution and Bylaws-Background and Resource Papers, circa 1973; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 1)
  - NEA-Executive Secretary (T. Herndon), December 1973-September 1974; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 12)
    Herndon, Terry
  - NEA-Follow-Up Planning Committee [file 1/2], November 1968-January 1970; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 13)
  - NEA-Follow-Up Planning Committee [file 2/2], November 1968-January 1970; Series 5 (Box 1180, Folder 14)
  - NEA-Health Services Guidelines, May 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 1)
  - NEA-Higher Education (General Correspondence), November 1972; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 2)
  - NEA-In-Service Education Project, May 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 3)
  - NEA-International Relations, November 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 4)
  - NEA-Merger, Affiliation Policy, May 1974-December 1975; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 5)
  - NEA-New Appointees, March 1974-April 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 6)
  - NEA-Newspaper Clippings, November 1975; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 7)
  - NEA-Office of Convention and Conference Management, April 1973-August 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 8)
  - NEA-Office of General Counsel, November 1973; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 9)
  - NEA-Overseas Centers, April 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 10)
  - NEA-Parking Rules and Regulations, June 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 11)
  - NEA-Personnel Changes, August 1975; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 12)
  - NEA-Planning Office, August 1973; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 13)
  - NEA-PAC, March 1973-May 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 14)
  - NEA-Publications, Sales, May 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 15)
  - NEA Relationships with National Power Groups Report Number 2, April 1972; series 5 (Box 4332, Folder 12)
  - NEA-Research Division, October 1973-November 1973; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 16)
  - NEA-Retirement, March 1973-February 1976; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 17)
  - NEA-Special Services, 1973-1975; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 18)
  - NEA-Structure (Units, Etc.), 1972-1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 19)
  - NEA-SNEA Committee, 1975; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 20)
  - NEA-Survey-4 Day Work Week, July 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 21)
  - NEA-Teacher Rights, November 1973; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 22)
  - NEA's Financial Situation, November 1977; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 23)
  - NEAMO, September 1973-April 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 24)
  - NEA Policy-Promotions, May 1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 25)
  - NEASO-In-Service Education Committee, March 1973; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 26)
  - National Planning, September 1975-December 1975; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 27)
  - "The Nature of Conflict", March 1977; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 28)
  - New Hampshire Education Association, 1973-1974; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 29)
  - New York City Project, September 1977; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 30)
  - New York Education Association, April 1976; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 31)
  - New York Education Association-Constitution and Bylaws, March 1977; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 32)
  - Next Step in the Implementation of Excellence in Local-State-National Relationships, January 1977-February 1977; Series 5 (Box 1181, Folder 33)
  - Objectives-Three Year Program Planning Forecast, August 1975-October 1975; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 1)
  - Objectives-Approved by NEA Board, November 1974; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 2)
  - Objectives-Final as of October 1975, Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 3)
  - Objectives-Response from Governance, 1976; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 4)
  - One Reason-One Vote, circa 1973; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 5)
  - Organization and Staff Relations Charts, 1955-1970; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 6)
  - Organization Charts (Jack's Lectures), April 1977; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 7)
  - "Organizational Change in the Profession", May 1969; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 8)
  - Organizational Change in the Profession, circa 1969; series 5 (Box 4332, Folder 13)
  - Outline-Briefing for Tuesday's Session, January 1969; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 9)
  - Outline for Summary Committees, circa 1969; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 10)
  - Outline-"Where We Are Now", January 1969; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 11)
  - Overseas Education Association, February 1975; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 12)
  - Pattern Under New Constitution, September 1974; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 13)
  - Pennsylvania State Education Association, March 1975; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 14)
  - Performance Apprasial Policy, October 1973-March 1976; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 15)
  - Performance Review, April 1978-June 1978; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 16)
  - Personnel Administration-Title Number Guide, June 1974; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 17)
  - "A Plan of Action" (Urban Services Division), 1967-1968; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 18)
  - Planning Office-All General Correspondence, September 1974-November 1975; Series 5 (Box 1182, Folder 19)
  - Planning Office-Outgoing Correspondence, June 1970-December 1971; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 1)
  - Policy Observer Statement, January 1971; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 2)
  - Position Classification, November 1977-May 1978; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 3)
  - Position Descriptions, September 1973-October 1973; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 4)
  - PPBS (South Korean Development), November 1977; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 5)
  - Presentation on Financial Management to State Executive Secretaries, March 1973; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 6)
  - Program and Budget Committee, November 1975-February 1976; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 7)
  - Program-Budgeting Procedure Recommendation, circa 1970; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 8)
  - Program Development, 1974; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 9)
  - Program Evaluation Report Fiscal Year 1976-1977, Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 10)
  - A Program for NEA's Future, circa 1978; series 5 (Box 4351, Folder 2)
  - Program for NEA's Future, Special Committee on Financial Evaluation, circa 1978; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 11)
  - Program Inventory Report, December 1969; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 12)
  - Program-Planning Format (3 Year), 1975; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 13)
  - Proposal for an Intra-Governmental Council, April 1972; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 14)
  - Public Employees, 1971-1972; Series 5 (Box 1183, Folder 15)
  - "Relationships with National Power Groups", February 1972; Series 5 (Box 1184, Folder 1)
  - "Relationships with National Power Groups", April 1972-June 1972; Series 5 (Box 1184, Folder 2)
  - Relationships with Other Organizations (Charge from Board), 1970-1971; Series 5 (Box 1184, Folder 3)
  - Report of the Committee to Study the Need for an NEA Dues Increase, February 1975; Series 5 (Box 1184, Folder 4)
  - Report on 1977 Convention of NAPE, August 1977-October 1977; Series 5 (Box 1184, Folder 5)
  - Report and Recommendations: NEA Constitutional Convention, May 1971; series 5 (Box 4332, Folder 14)
  - Report on Review of Status and Needs of Affiliates for NEA Staff Assistance, 1976-1977; Series 5 (Box 1184, Folder 6)
  - Report to NEA Board of Directors (Plans for 1972-1973), June 1972; Series 5 (Box 1184, Folder 7)
  - Report to Constitutional Convention-Distribution List, 1971; Series 5 (Box 1184, Folder 8)
  - Reports-Drafts, 1969-1971; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 2)
  - Reports-"Excellence in Local-State-National Relationships", June 1973; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 3)
  - Reports-"Higher Education in the United States: An Overview", 1973; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 4)
  - Reports-"NEA Relationships with National Power Groups, Report #2", April 1972; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 5)
  - Reports-"NEA Relationships with National Power Groups, Supplementary Volume: Appendixes", February 1972; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 6)
  - Reports-"Opinions of Delegates to 1972 NEA Representative Assembly Concerning NEA Goals, Objectives, and Activities", Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 7)
  - Reports-"Preliminary Report, NEA Relationships with National Power Groups", February 1972; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 8)
  - Reports-"Problems of City Teachers", 1973; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 9)
  - Reports-"Report and Recommendations, NEA Constitutional Convention", February 1971; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 10)
  - Reports-"Report and Recommendations, NEA Constitutional Convention", March 1971; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 11)
  - Reports-"Report and Recommendations, NEA Constitutional Convention", May 1971; Series 5 (Box 1587, Folder 12)